(Leonard:)-What about me?
-I'm sorry, Leonard...
(Sheldon:)...it's too early to discount the possibility
of this being an inside job.
(Leonard:)Would I be completely out of line
to ask you to shoot him?
(Policeman:)I'd be happy to put him under
a 72-hour psychiatric hold.
(Sheldon:)I'm not crazy.
My mother had me tested.
We're done. Call this number,
and we'll fax you a copy of the report.
(Policeman:)You can submit it
to your insurance company.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, that's the end
of your inquiry?
(Policeman:)Do you have any more information
that might be relevant?
(Sheldon:)Goodness. Where do I begin?
For instance, my laptop...
(Sheldon:)...contained four out of the five
gedanken experiments necessary...
...for a restatement of
the quantum measurement problem.
How's that going to help them?
(Sheldon:)They could monitor
scientific publications...
(Sheldon:)...and see if anyone posts such
a restatement in the next couple of months.
(Sheldon:)If so, the authors are most likely
in possession of my stolen laptop.
(Policeman:)Good night, fellas.
(Policeman:)Come on, Bochco.